Junaid Shahid

10 July 1995

Address: House 24, Street 40, G13/2, Islamabad,

Pakistan

Email: Junaidshahid910@gmail.com

Mobile: +92 302 4284248



OVERVIEW

Hospitality professional with 1 year experience

I am a Hospitality Professional with a Graduate Diploma in Hospitality & Tourism Management. I have 1 year of experience at three reputable Hospitality organizations. My strengths include, Building Connections, Efficient problem solving. Enthusiasm, Commitment, Organized and Thorough I am looking for a full-time position in Hospitality industry.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sales & Marketing Executive

FALCON ADVENTURE CLUB, ISLAMABAD, PAKISTAN

May 2018 - Present

Key responsibilities included:

- Identify Key marketing opportunities and advertise/market new offers from company on all mediums especially on social media
- Carrying out effective research & intelligence into competitor products & other trends.
- To make proposals for the customized events for individual and corporate clients.

Food & Beverage Trainee

PEARL CONTINENTAL HOTELS & RESORTS, RAWALPINDI, PAKISTAN

Feb 2018 – March 2018

Key responsibilities included:

Food & Beverage Operations

- > 2 weeks of experience in Food & Beverage Operations
- Maintained knowledge of current menu items garnishes ingredients and preparation methods.
- Set tables in assigned area, or check to see that they have been set correctly and uniformly using clean pressed linen, clean unspotted silverware; clean china, clean unspotted glassware.
- Deliver exceptional service by greeting and serving customers in a timely friendly manner.

Banquet Sales & Operations

- > 6 weeks of experience in Banquet Sales & Operations
- Provided administrative and general support to both the sales and catering team.
- Communicate and collaborate all event details with a variety of departments within the hotel operation.
- Responsible for multitasking at multiple events and daily operation

Housekeeping Trainee

GRAND AMBASSADOR HOTEL, ISLAMABAD, PAKISTAN

Dec 2017 - Jan 2018

Key responsibilities included:

- > 4 Weeks of experience in Housekeeping
- Replenish stock of items in hotel rooms
- Monitor rooms for general repairs and upkeep
- Inspect guest rooms prior to checking in
- Accommodate requests by guests for extra towels, ice bucket, pillows and blankets

QUALIFICATIONS

Graduate Diploma in Hospitality & Tourism Management

COLLEGE OF TOURISM & HOTEL MANAGEMENT - COTHM, ISLMABAD,

PAKISTAN

2016 – 17

Coursework: Hospitality & Tourism Management, F&B Operations, H&T Marketing, Mastering Communications, Front Office Operations, Human

Resources, Accounting

Intermediate in Commerce (HSSC)

SUPERIOR COLLEGE, BUREWALA, PAKISTAN

2014 - 2016

Matriculation in Science (SSC)

DIVISIONAL PUBLIC SCHOOL, BUREWALA, PAKISTAN

2011 - 2013

SKILLS

Soft Skills

Interpersonal Skill, Communication Skill, Problem Solving Team Management, Facilitating Skill, Presentation Skill, Confident

Computer Skills
Microsoft Word, PowerPoint, Excel, Internet

Lingual SkillsEnglish, Urdu, Punjabi

INTERESTS

Culinary Arts Bartender Barista

Event Planning Interior Designing

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Done research projects during my Hospitality & Tourism Management study program.
- Hospitality & Tourism Industry in Swat and Terrorism.
- Role of Culture in the Emerging Industry of Hospitality in KPK
- Managing Events for Hospitality & Tourism Industry in case of ITB Berlin 2017
- Marketing Strategies for Hospitality & Tourism Industry in case of Second Cup Coffee Islamabad
- Strategic Impact of Business Environment in case of Atlantis Palm Islamabad

REFERENCES NAME: MR REHMAT HUSSAIN

DESIGNATION: BANQUET SALES MANAGER

COMPANY: PEARL CONTINENTAL HOTELS & RESORTS, RAWALPINDI,

PAKISTAN

MOBILE: +92 336 5256376

NAME: MR RIZWAN SAEED

DESGNATION: GENERAL MANAGER

COMPANY: GRAND AMBASSADOR HOTEL, ISLAMABAD, PAKISTAN

MOBILE: +92 300 5010088

NAME: MR ALI USMAN DESIGNATION: C E O

COMPANY: FALCON ADVENTURE CLUB, ISLAMABAD, PAKISTAN

MOBILE: +92 333 6287574